<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Swess</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Swess</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swess.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Half-Lambert Shader</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/half-lambert-shader/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/half-lambert-shader/</guid><description>Created a fully customized lighting Uber shader for our current project at Canorous Interactive, supporting nearly all the same features as Unity&amp;rsquo;s main Lit shader.
The Half-Lambert lighting term is utilized in various commercial games such as Team Fortress 2 and Valorant, and extensively described online. I won&amp;rsquo;t delve into the technical details and differences between the various lighting techniques, but here are some link for quick explanations and examples.</description></item><item><title>ScreenSpace Simulation</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/screenspace-simulation-vfx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/screenspace-simulation-vfx/</guid><description>This is a 2D simulation VFX driven by the pixel channels&amp;rsquo; values. From the initial snapshot, different channels and values are stored in texture buffers for the simulation to consume and modify.
In the example video below, an outward velocity vector is added so that the displacement is directed toward the edges of the screen.
Various controls are available for the simulation to achieve different results. For example, dissipation per color channel, viscosity, velocity direction, and intensity, among others.</description></item><item><title>Stylized Fog Shader</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/fogshader/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/fogshader/</guid><description>Stylized fog shader made in Unity (URP 12.1.14). This shader was made and used in our current project at Canorous Interactive for different contexts.
Controls over textures, colors, and different parameters renders it very flexible and allow for a very wide range of stylization and usecases.
This is not publicly available.</description></item><item><title>Stylized Arcs &amp; Sparkles VFX</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/teleportvfx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/teleportvfx/</guid><description>A VFX shader and particle system for stylized arcs and sparkles made in Unity (URP 12.1.14).
This was made and used in our current project at Canorous Interactive for different contexts and with different variants.
This is not publicly available.</description></item><item><title>Tile Pattern Tool</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/tile-pattern/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/tile-pattern/</guid><description>Procedural placement tool</description></item><item><title>Armageddon</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/armageddon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/armageddon/</guid><description>Ludum Dare 42 Compo Entry</description></item><item><title>Home Project</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/home/</guid><description>Small atmospheric and unique survival game made with Unity for the Global GameJam 2019.
The theme of the GGJ 2019 was: What home means to you
The prototype has been developed with a small team of 6 persons, including 2 programmers, 1 game designer &amp;amp; 3 artists. Our team, called JAMKIS, was part of the second season of JamNation.
The game brings you in an ancestral adventure where you play the role of an Inuit tasked to finish the construction of your igloo on time while maintaining your family alive and warm.</description></item><item><title>Safeguard the realm</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/safeguardtherealm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/safeguardtherealm/</guid><description>A tower defense concept combined with an auto-battler in-game progression inspiration.
This game project was executed as a team effort with 6 people in a course of Game Development at Concordia University.
Safeguard The Realm! is a tower defense game where the right strategy is absolutely necessary in order to not lose. The objective of the game is to defend the castle against waves of enemies, by placing various types of defense towers on the grid map.</description></item><item><title>The Forge Launcher</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/theforge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/theforge/</guid><description>Game launcher</description></item><item><title>U.N.I.T.Y.</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/unity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/unity/</guid><description>A 4 players local competitive arcade game that doesn’t take itself seriously</description></item></channel></rss>