<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GameJam on Swess</title><link>https://swess.github.io/tags/gamejam/</link><description>Recent content in GameJam on Swess</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://swess.github.io/tags/gamejam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Armageddon</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/armageddon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/armageddon/</guid><description>Ludum Dare 42 Compo Entry</description></item><item><title>Home Project</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/home/</guid><description>Small atmospheric and unique survival game made with Unity for the Global GameJam 2019.
The theme of the GGJ 2019 was: What home means to you
The prototype has been developed with a small team of 6 persons, including 2 programmers, 1 game designer &amp;amp; 3 artists. Our team, called JAMKIS, was part of the second season of JamNation.
The game brings you in an ancestral adventure where you play the role of an Inuit tasked to finish the construction of your igloo on time while maintaining your family alive and warm.</description></item><item><title>Safeguard the realm</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/safeguardtherealm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/safeguardtherealm/</guid><description>A tower defense concept combined with an auto-battler in-game progression inspiration.
This game project was executed as a team effort with 6 people in a course of Game Development at Concordia University.
Safeguard The Realm! is a tower defense game where the right strategy is absolutely necessary in order to not lose. The objective of the game is to defend the castle against waves of enemies, by placing various types of defense towers on the grid map.</description></item><item><title>U.N.I.T.Y.</title><link>https://swess.github.io/projects/unity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swess.github.io/projects/unity/</guid><description>A 4 players local competitive arcade game that doesn’t take itself seriously</description></item></channel></rss>